公司给我们发了这该死的智能手机
Work gave us these stupid smartphones,
老娘根本就不懂用
and I don't know how to use it.
请问您需要什么帮助
How can I help you?
我跟你说了  别再打电话给我了
I told you, stop calling me.
你打错电话了
You have the wrong number.
别再烦我老婆了
Leave my wife alone.
您是想离开您的老婆吗
You'd like to leave your wife?
正在搜索您所在区域的离婚律师
Searching for divorce attorneys in your area.
我可没这么说  你这家庭破坏狂魔
That's not what I said, home wrecker!
二位  二位  那并不是真人
Guys, guys, guys, that's not a person.
那是个智能私人助理系统
It's an automated personal assistant.
等你搞清楚那手机的各种酷炫功能
When you figure out all the cool stuff that phone does,
你一定会爱死它的
you're gonna love it.
好吧  我们的经理也是这么说的
Yeah, that's what our manager at work said.
然后她宣布了一堆新的公司规章制度
And then she hit us with a ton of new corporate policies.
他们要求我们把打扫的那些房子拍下来
They want us to take pictures of the houses we clean.
摆明了不信任我们嘛
Which means they don't trust us.
真烦  这样我们就得真枪实弹地搞打扫了
Which sucks 'cause now we have to really clean the houses.
至少你有了一款酷炫的新手机啊
Well, at least you got a cool new phone out of it.
我讨厌这个  太复杂了
I hate it. It's too complicated.
在上班路上  我的屁股不小心打给伯特三次
I butt-dialed Burt three times on the way to work.
你的屁股虽然说不了话
Your butt makes up for in appearance
但至少长得不错
what it lacks in communication skills.
那可真了不起
That's pretty impressive.
我的屁股只有两个功能
My butt has only two tricks.
第一个  恶心了点
One is, uh, disgusting,
另一个就是穿上牛仔裤看着很正
and the other is looking amazing in jeans.
既然你现在有了新手机
Now that you have a new phone,
你可以在维基视频上关注我
you can follow me on WikiVids.
维基视频是什么
What's WikiVids?
是个网站  我把自己煎好的蛋拍成视频传上去
It's a site where I post videos of the eggs I make
再加上一些有趣的评论
and my funny little comments about them.
我其实就是描述一下它们的外形
I kind of interpret what they look like.
我把这个称作"小野洋蛋"
I call this one "Yolko Ono."
影射小野洋子导致列侬婚姻的破裂
看到那个蛋把薯饼分成两半了吗
See how the egg broke up the hash browns?
瞧瞧啊
Oh, look at that.
那简直是艺术啊
Now, that is art.
你应该开个博物馆
You should open up a museum
把这些菜端上来
where you bring these out to people,
人们可以去吃
and then they get to eat it.
那不就是个餐馆吗
Isn't that just a restaurant?
什么都被别人先想到了
Everything's been done!
其实  如果你那么讨厌自己的手机
You know, if you hate your phone so much,
我们可以换一下的
we could switch phones.
我的翻盖手机拍照很模糊的
My flip phone takes lousy pictures,
那样的话  你就不用打扫得那么干净了
so you don't have to clean that good.
是啊  我觉得我们是可以...
Yeah, I guess we could do...
他想要从我们这里得到东西
He wants something from us.
我们也要从他那里获得一些好处
We should get something in return.
你是想玩  "选口袋  选口袋
You thinking "Pick-a-Pocket, Pick-a-Pocket,
口袋里的东西统统交出来"的游戏吗
We Want Everything in Your Pockets"?
今天是个好时机  吉米穿的是多袋工作裤
It's a good day for it. Jimmy's wearing cargo pants.
我们能让他跳一下吗
Ooh, can we make him jump?
不行  不行  你们知道规则的
No, no, no, no, no, you know the rules.
一次转身一个口袋  不许摸不许反悔
One turn, one pocket, no touching, no whining.
我要选
I-I'm gonna go...
右边  左边
right... left...
右边那只前口袋
Right front!
该死  怎么着我们都是拿到手机
Oh, damn, we were getting that anyway.
其他口袋里都有些什么
What was in the other pockets?
钥匙
Keys!
钱包
Wallet!
水果派
Fruit pie!
天啊  我们该对水果派下手的
Oh, man, we could have had a fruit pie!
我想再来一个面包卷
I want another roll.
抱歉  曾奶奶  我做得不够
Sorry, Maw Maw, I didn't make enough
不够你们各分两个
for both of you to have two.
你只能和喜旺平分了
You're gonna have to split it with Hope.
话说  在新的公司规章制度上
You know, there's a lot of really great stuff
加了很多好规定啊
in these new corporate policies.
一周带薪年假
I mean, a week's paid vacation,
-401K -401千米
- 401K... - 401K?
401K为美国养老保险制度
音同410千米
免了  谢谢
No, thanks.
我之前跑了五千米就差点吐了
I ran a 5K once and almost puked.
嘿  你竟然有医疗保险呢
Oh, hey, you get health care.
实际上  这保险范围还包括配偶
Actually, it says spouses are covered, too.
你们终于能看得起医生了
You guys could finally go to the doctor.
我们可没生病
We're not sick.
不必非得等生病了再去看医生吧
You don't have to be sick to go to the doctor.
如果没生病  干嘛去看医生啊
Why would you go to a doctor if you're not sick?
难道是去打招呼吗
Like, to say hello?
你好啊  医生
Hello, Doctor.
你好  伯特  你还好吗
Hello, Burt. How are you?
反正没病
Not sick.
太好了  谢谢你顺道来看我
Wonderful. Thanks for stopping by.
好吧
Fine.
好好享受你的碳水化合物吧  小胖子
Enjoy the carbs, fatso.
吃碳水化合物易长胖
各位  你们必须定期做检查
Guys, you have to get checkups.
不然小毛病会变成大问题的
Otherwise little things, they turn into big things.
小洞不补  大洞吃苦
It only takes one spark to burn down the whole forest.
我唯一看的医生就是殷道道
The only doctor I go to is Dr. Vajajay.
他是印度人  名字就是那样的
He's Indian. That's his name.
他是我的妇科医生
He looks after my hoo-hah.
真恶心
Gross.
我敢跟你保证  一点都不恶心
I assure you, it is not.
好了  这是勒布朗・詹姆斯和飞天巨桃
Okay, this is LeBron James and the Giant Peach.
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
我打算将水果和蔬菜弄成著名运动员的样子
I'm gonna make videos of fruits and vegetables
然后拍些视频
made to look like famous athletes.
我这里有韦恩・葡萄茨基[冰球运动员]
I've got Wayne Grapesky,
梨・布莱恩[贝尔・布莱恩/橄榄球运动员]
Pear Bryant.
我还在想一个棒球选手
Uh, I'm trying to think of a baseball player
可以用草莓来弄  不过
I could use for strawberries, but...
暂时没什么灵感
nothing's coming to me.
你不觉得这不够原创吗
Don't you think it's a little derivative?
不  那是个大桃子呢
No, it's a big peach.
我是说这不是你自己的主意
I mean it's not very original.
我也是拍食物的
I do food.
你这是在抄袭我的创意
You're just copying my idea.
那又怎样  不过是愚蠢的视频而已
So? It's just a silly video thing.
愚蠢的视频而已
A silly video thing?
我觉得那28位
I think the 28 people
关注"塞布丽娜每日蛋黄秀"的人
who follow "Sabrina's Yolk of the Day"
可不同意你的观点
might disagree with you.
等一下
Wait a minute.
草莓・邦兹
Strawberry Bonds.
贝瑞・邦兹  美国职业棒球选手
我真是够蠢的
Oh, how dumb am I?
你脚趾上那个斑怎么了
What's going on with your toe freckle?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
我有点担心  它越来越大了
I'm worried it's getting bigger.
或许是因为你的脚趾变小了吧
Maybe your toe is getting smaller.
那也一样令人担忧啊
Well, that worries me, too.
不管是哪个原因
Either one of those things
都可能是最终酿成大祸的小火星
could be the spark that starts the fire.
那是塞布丽娜关于医生的看法
That's what Sabrina said about the doctor.
我也在想那事  听着
I've been thinking about that, too. Listen.
我觉得我的脖子响得更严重了
I think my neck crack's getting worse.
就好像有人在我脑袋底下做爆米花
Sounds like someone's making popcorn under my head.
我的耳朵也会时不时很痛
Sometimes my ear just starts hurting.
比如我站在某个地方
Like, I'll just be standing somewhere,
然后突然间
and then, suddenly, ow!
又疼了吗
Did it just happen?
没有  我在演啦
No, I was just dramatizing.
每周也就一两次
It only happens a couple times a week.
你知道吗  我有时撒尿
You know what else? Sometimes when I pee,
尿会分叉
it comes out in two different directions.
我也只是在演而已
I'm dramatizing, too.
我早餐后会眼皮跳
My after-breakfast eye twitch
现在有时会一直持续到午餐时间
is now sometimes lasting all the way till lunch.
无论我喝多少咖啡来放松自己
No matter how much coffee I drink to relax myself,
就是停不下来
it just doesn't stop!
我这样做的时候  下巴会疼得超厉害
My jaw hurts like crazy when I go like this.
-那看起来就很疼  -没错
- Ooh, that looks painful. - It is.
我不想承认  但是塞布丽娜说得对
I hate to say it, but maybe Sabrina was right.
我们该去看医生了
We need to see a doctor.
也许有些事情上她是对的
Maybe she was right about other things.
你真信世界上有个叫乍得的国家吗[非洲国家]
Do you really think there's a country called Chad?
信啊  而且那里的每个人都带着网球拍
Yeah, and everyone there carries a a tennis racket
披着一件毛衣  袖子系在肩上
and wears a sweater tied around their shoulders.
我开始焦虑了
I'm starting to get worried.
每项症状我都有
I think I have everything.
肌无力  有
Muscle weakness? Check.
疲劳  有
Fatigue? Check.
付款方式  有
Form of payment? Check.
我知道  我会眩晕吗
I know. Do I get dizzy?
如果你一直转圈的话
When you spin around a lot.
该死
Damn it!
维吉妮亚・吉斯
Virginia Chance?
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
中招了
Gotcha!
我喜欢这招
I love that one.
对我所有的新病人都玩这招
Do it to all my new patients.
我的理念是  没保险的话
My philosophy is, laughter is the best medicine.
开怀大笑是一方良药
Unless you have insurance.
有保险的话  那药就是最好的药
In that case, medicine is the best medicine.
好了
Okay.
进来检查吧
Let's go look under your hood.
要坚强哦
Stay strong.
毫迪超市
各位  我一般不发什么东西洒了的视频  但是
Hey, guys, I don't usually post spill videos, but...
长着林肯的头的鳄鱼也不是每天都能看到的
you don't see a crocodile with Abe Lincoln's head every day.
各位
Guys?
好了
All right, well,
这太逗了  但我们应该
that was an amusing diversion, but we should...
你知道吗  鸡可以明天再漂白
Oh, you know what? We can bleach the chicken tomorrow.
咱再看一遍吧
Let's watch it again.
你们在看我的"今日蛋黄秀"视频吗
You guys watching my daily "Yolk of the Day" Video?
不是  吉米在维基视频发了一段超搞笑的
No. Jimmy posted this hilarious new WikiVid.
你可能该去查查你的胆固醇水平了
And you should probably get your cholesterol checked.
让我看看
Let me see this.
最好别跟食物有关
This better not be food-related.
我从来都不喜欢三个臭皮匠
I was never a fan of the Three Stooges.
吉米@维基视频
我觉得他们满身是汗  笨手笨脚
I found them sweaty and clumsy
一点也不好玩
and not very entertaining.
说直白点  我就是这么叫
To be clear, the Three Stooges
威尔弗里德的生殖器的
is what I called Wilfrid's genitals.
除非你也上年纪了
Unless you are one,
不然老年人都很有意思的
old people are funny.
是啊  我觉得挺有意思的
Yeah. I guess it's funny.
就是太没技术含量了
It's a little simple.
没技术含量
Simple?
是啊  当你有27个粉丝时
Yeah. I mean, when you have as many
他们希望你从艺术和理智层面上
as 27 followers, they want you to challenge them
去挑战他们
artistically and intellectually.
我还以为你有28个粉丝呢
Oh, I thought you had 28.
我原来有
I did.
很抱歉  塞布丽娜
I'm sorry, Sabrina,
但看完跳小鸡舞的修女
but between the nun that does the chicken dance,
弹钢琴的小猫
the cat that plays the piano
和詹姆士的搞笑新视频
and James' hysterical new videos,
我实在看不出来那些蛋
I don't have the time to stare at eggs
哪里像史蒂夫・布西密[演员]
until they look like Steve Buscemi.
好啦
All done.
你都成瞎子了
Oh, you've gone blind.
我们早就该来了
We should have come sooner.
我没瞎
I'm not blind.
他们做眼部检查时  会屏蔽你的瞳孔
When they give you an eye exam, they delete your pupils.
但好消息就是  我唯一的毛病就是我的眼睛
But the good news is, the only thing wrong with me is my eyes.
戴副眼镜就没问题啦
Nothing glasses can't fix.
小方子而已
It's just a slight prescription.
就  就好比是从标准画质提升到高清画质
It... it'd be like going from standard definition to high-def.
很抱歉你不得不...
And I'm sorry you have to make such a...
出这么大个洋相
spectacle of yourself.
你一旦发现自己不是将死之人
He's a lot more funny once you find out
他就好玩多了  你会懂的
you're not dying. You'll see.
尽管花了87年的时间
Well, it took 87 years,
塞布丽娜@维基视频
但现在  我的脖子终于看起来像我的阴道了
but now, officially, my neck looks like my vagina.
她的脖子看起来确实像阴道
Her neck does look like a vagina.
塞布丽娜在哪里
Where's Sabrina?
她半个小时前去休息了
She took her, uh, break a half hour ago.
不公平  知道吗
No fair, all right?
你说我的视频"非研窜"
You said that my video was deflippititive,
现在你才是"非研窜"
and now you're being defibrilitive.
我想你要说的词是非原创
I think the word you're looking for is derivative.
无所谓  好吧  如果我不能拍食物
Whatever. All right, if I can't film food,
那你也不能利用我的疯狂曾祖母
then you can't take advantage of my crazy great-grandmother
来娱乐陌生人
to amuse strangers.
-那是我的创意  -拜托
- That's my thing. - Come on.
你和我都应该想录什么就录什么
You and I should both be able to record whatever we want...
还真是有27个粉丝的人说出来的话
Sounds like someone with 27 followers talking.
35个了  非常感谢你
35. Thank you very much.
35啊  我记得我有35个粉丝
Oh, 35. I remember when I had 35 followers.
都已经是  新增四个粉丝以前的事了
that was... four followers ago.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
你的手机是粉色的
Well, your phone is pink.
是啊  无所谓啊  35粉
Yep. Whatever, 35.
都检查完了  你的眼睛
Well, everything checks out-- your eyes,
你的心脏  血压都没问题  你很健康
your heart, blood pressure. You're in great shape.
那还不错嘛
Well, that wasn't so bad.
我考虑每隔六七年
I might think about getting a regular checkup
做一次常规检查
every six or seven years.
有的检测其实还挺有意思的
Some of those tests were actually kind of fun.
再用那个小锤子给我敲一敲
Do that little hammer again.
太刺激了
That is wild!
敲身体其他部位也会这样吗
Does that work on other parts of the body, too?
这样我就可以在卧室里用神奇的锤子了
'Cause I could really use that magic hammer in the bedroom.
还有一件事
Just, uh, one more thing.
转身  弯腰  然后
Just turn around, bend over and...
保证你会保守秘密
promise you can keep a secret.
没问题
All right.
感觉像是你的手指插进了我的后庭
And that feels like your finger in my doggy door.
这只是一项常规检查  伯特
Oh, it's just a routine test, Burt.
如果你是想让我的膝盖动起来
Well, if you're trying to get my knee to move again,
恭喜你  它现在抖得厉害  你可以停手了
it's twitching pretty good, so you can stop now.
我感觉你的前列腺摸有些湿软
Your prostate feels a little... boggy.
我感觉你的手指有点粗大
And your finger feels a little biggy. Oh!
你多久行一次房事
How of... how often do you have sex?
像这样吗  从没有过
Like this? Never.
不是  是跟你老婆
No, like, with your wife.
行房事对你的前列腺有好处
Sex can be good for your prostate.
我记好了
I'll keep that in mind.
我还要做个结肠镜检查
In the meantime, I want to do a colonoscopy
确保你没有更大的毛病
just to make sure this isn't a sign of a larger problem.
好  总不会比现在做的事更不爽吧
Fine. Can't be any worse than what we're doing now.
我们要从你的肛门插进一个光纤摄像机
Well, we pass a fiber-optic camera through your anus,
稍微查看一下里面的情况
and we have a little look-see.
我错了
I stand corrected.
简直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
世界如此清晰
Everything's so clear.
鸟儿  云儿
The birds, the clouds...
连对街的公交长椅我都看得到
I can even see that bus bench all the way across the street.
眼镜世界全场半价
"50% off glasses at Glasses Land."
要是一个小时前看到的就好了
That would've been nice to know an hour ago.
快走  医生说我要多行房事
Come on, the doctor said I have to have
让我的结肠不那么湿软
more sex to un-bog my colon.
按方抓药  你的药抓好了  现在该我了
You got your prescription filled; now it's my turn.
虽然他没有清楚地把药方写下来
He didn't actually write it down,
但我觉得应该每日两次  饭后服用
but I'm thinking twice daily after meals.
开路
Here we go.
简直不敢相信世界如此清晰
I can't believe e how clear everything is.
海伦・凯勒[盲人作家]戴上眼镜后
This is probably what Helen Keller felt like
应该也是这感觉
when she got her glasses.
我第一次这么兴奋地复习迎考
This is the first test I'm actually excited to study for.
"灌输式学习"这个词是不是就是这么来的
I wonder if this is how they came up with the term "Cramming."
这边真该好好重漆一下了
We really need to paint out here.
维吉妮亚
Virginia...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
这地毯真是脏死了
This carpet is really stained.
专心点
Focus.
是香蕉皮啊
Oh, that's a banana peel.
之前还以为是我的手链
I thought it was my bracelet.
不行  我没法在这滚床单  伯特
No. I can't have sex in here, Burt.
-这屋子太恶心了  -把眼镜摘了
- This house is disgusting. - Take the glasses off.
好主意
Oh, good idea.
不行  我做不到啊
No, I can't do this.
我总是在想象我看不到的一切
I just keep imagining everything I'm not seeing.
或许你可以专注于
Well, maybe you should start focusing
你眼前看到的
on what you are seeing.
天呐  你跳性感舞步的时候
Oh, my God... is that the face
就是这幅表情吗
you make when you do your sexy dance?
这副眼镜真是坑爹神器
Ah, these glasses are ruining everything!
老爸
Oh, hey, Dad.
怎么样
How's it going?
我要在一个小时内喝掉一加仑泻药
I got to drink a gallon of laxative in an hour.
好消息是
On the plus side,
我三年级时吞掉的那枚水牛镍币
I'm pretty sure that buffalo nickel
终于要重见天日了
I swallowed in third grade is finally gonna resurface.
好吧
Okay, well...
去看看疯狂的曾奶奶
time to go see if crazy Maw Maw
能不能让我粉丝破50了
can help me break 50 followers.
曾奶奶
Hey, uh, Maw Maw,
胃又堵上了吗
you, uh, got anything stuck in your craw today?
没有  我只是在清理肠胃
No, I just cleaned my craw.
继续说
Keep talking.
你的卧室怎么闻起来像我妈的口气
Why does your bedroom smell like my mother's breath?
我发现地摊上有些酒渍
I found some wine stains on the carpet,
又洗不掉
and I couldn't get them out,
所以我就想让它看起来
so I'm gonna make it look like
像是杰克逊・波兰的画作
one of those Jackson Polack paintings.
嗯  也是个办法
Sure, that's one way of doing it.
有了这副破眼镜
With these damn glasses,
这屋子里的所有小毛病我都看得清清楚楚
I notice every little imperfection around the house.
把那个绿色的记号笔递给我
Hand me that green magic marker.
外面有株植物需要润一下色
I saw a plant outside that needs a touch-up.
这是个好题材
That sounds very sensible.
维吉妮亚过度清洁  第一幕
Virginia obsessively cleaning, take one.
好一点了
That's a little better.
还行
That could work.
准备好了
Ready!
把门关上  跟下雪了似的
Shut the door. It looks like it's snowing in here--
空气中灰尘太多了
there's so much dust floating in the air. Ooh.
我想让你摘了眼镜
I'd say take the glasses off,
但你这幅萨拉・佩林的样子让我很性奋啊
but the whole Sarah Palin thing is really working for me.
美国女政治家
戴眼镜 曾猎杀驼鹿
跟我说说你猎杀过的驼鹿吧
Can you tell me about a moose you shot?
有人已经开始动起来了嘛
Ooh. Someone's in the mood.
不对  是我的胃
No, that's my stomach.
先前喝的结肠饮料
I think the pre-colonoscopy beverage
效果有点...
is doing something crazy to my... Uh-oh.
热翔来袭
Hot soup!
我感觉我之前喝掉了一个瀑布
It's like I ate a waterfall!
看呐  今早第一大事
Look at this. First thing this morning,
我新增了三个粉丝
and I've already got three new followers.
太好了你回来了
Thank God you're here.
快送我去医院
I need a ride to the hospital.
求助  送我去做结肠镜检查
我不想用这个牌子
I did not want to use this sign.
维吉妮亚呢
Where's Virginia?
请告诉我她又在疯狂搞卫生
Please tell me she's obsessively cleaning something.
她把自己锁在我们的卧室里
She's locked herself in our bedroom.
中大奖了
Jackpot.
最后一次叫你  维吉妮亚
Last chance, Virginia!
再等一下
Just need another minute!
这幅死样子怎么出去见人
I can't go out in public looking like this.
维吉妮亚  开门
Hey, Virginia. Open up!
外面有些棕色树叶
Saw some brown leaves outside
需要润点色
that could use a fresh coat of paint.
真讨厌
Oh, dang.
开个缝  让我把手塞进去就行
Hey, I-I just want to stick my arm in.
曾奶奶
Hey, Maw Maw.
奥巴马真是个天才
Obama's a genius.
一二三
And... go.
不许你再拍我了
You're not filming me anymore.
我知道你想干什么
I know what you're up to.
昨天我去毫迪超市了
Yesterday, I was at Howdy's.
曾奶奶  告诉我接下来发生了什么
Maw Maw, tell me what happened next.
然后我就告诉罗莎・帕克斯我挪不开
So I told Rosa Parks I couldn't move over
美国黑人人民权主义者
因为我拎了太多购物袋
because I had all these shopping bags.
谁知道她会小题大做
Who knew she was gonna turn it
闹出这么大名堂
into such a big to-do?
那个满脸褶子的疯婆子
Hey, that crazy, wrinkled old bitty
偷了我的故事
is stealing all my stories.
坐在我的浴缸里  还戴着我的浴帽
In my bathtub, wearing my shower cap!
等一下  我明白了
Wait a minute. I know what's going on.
有人
Somebo...
糟了  又忘了
Oh, crap. Lost it.
告诉我怎么回事
Tell me what's going on.
他们把一切都招了
They told me everything.
不许再拍我
I'm cutting you off.
别这样嘛  曾奶奶
Come on, Maw Maw.
我没啥别的可录了
I've got nothing else to film.
好了  吉米  出发了
All right, Jimmy, let's go.
我可不想错过预约
I don't want to miss my appointment
再忍受一次术前准备的煎熬
and go through that prep again.
再拉下去  70年代就停产的那些麦片
At the end there, I was pooping out cereals
都要被我拉出来了
they haven't made since the '70s.
我一点都不喜欢这个主意
I do not like the idea of this one bit.
我见过的最小的摄像机是装在手表上的
The smallest camera I've ever seen was on a watch,
哪怕那么小  插进去的时候都会刮伤
and that would still scrape going in.
把它看成一种医疗器械就好  别当它是摄像机
Yeah, well, just think of it as a medical device, not as a camera.
不过是一根五英尺长的小管子
It's just a little tube that's five feet long.
死亡概率极低
"In the unlikely event of death..."
天啊
Oh, my God.
医生
Doc!
这上面说  我可能会送命
This says I could die.
你之前没跟我说
You didn't tell me that.
就是个免责申明
That's just the disclaimer
所有要接受全身麻醉的病人都要签的
for anyone going under general anesthetic.
别担心  伯特
Don't worry, Burt.
全麻的死亡概率只有万分之一
Only one out of every 10,000 people dies while they're under.
你做过多少起这种手术
How many of these have you done?
差不多一万起吧
About 10,000.
从没出过问题
Never had a problem.
吉米
Jimmy...
到一万了还没死过人
he's overdue for a death.
所以要轮到我了  我有预感
It's gonna be me. I can feel it.
带我出去
Get me the hell out of here.
我不想死的时候  菊花里还插着摄像机
I don't want to die with a camera up my poop chute.
老爸  都说了死亡率低了
Dad, it says "Unlikely."
死亡率低  概率低的事天天都在发生
"Unlikely"? Unlikely things happen all the time.
迈尔克・乔丹长出了希特勒的胡子
Michael Jordan grew a Hitler mustache.
简直莫名其妙  莫名其妙
That came out of nowhere. Nowhere!
吉米・吉斯又传新视频了
Jimmy Chance has done it again.
也许没那么糟啊
It can't be that bad.
确实不太乐观
Ooh. That's not good.
-我能挤爆它吗  -不
- Can I pop it? Just... - No!
戴上眼镜之后  我的生活变得愈发悲催
Ever since I got these glasses, they've just made my life worse.
先是看清了这个屋子有多不堪
First, I saw how worn-out this house was,
等我擦干净家里的镜子后
and then when I started cleaning the mirrors,
又发现  不堪的不止是这个屋子
I saw the house wasn't the only thing looking a little worn.
不是所有人都买得起新衣服
Well, not everyone can afford new clothes.
我衣服怎么了
What's the matter with my clothes?
没什么
Oh. Nothing.
我说的是我的脸
I was talking about my face.
我试着往脸上涂更多的化妆品
I tried wearing more makeup
整理发型
and fixing my hair,
但胭脂水粉之下  我还是能看见
but underneath all that, I still got these little lines
眼角的细纹和黑眼圈
and dark circles under my eyes.
维吉妮亚  你还是很漂亮的
Virginia, you still look great.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
但我已经不是25岁时的水嫩样了
But I don't look 25.
至少也得看着像28啊
I could pass for 28, tops.
可伯特在这副眼镜之下变得更帅了
But these damn glasses make Burt look even better,
我知道  他最终会意识到
and I just know that eventually he's gonna realize
我会慢慢人老珠黄
I'm not the hot piece of ass I was one or two months ago.
人们不是常说
Don't some people say that it's what's
内心美才是最重要的吗
on the inside that counts?
是啊  丑人都这么说
Yeah. Ugly people.
以前伯特和我常常一起嘲笑
Burt and I used to make fun of people
说这种话的人
who said things like that.
现在他也会嘲笑我了
Now he's gonna be making fun of me.
我确定他现在还没心思想这事呢
Pretty sure he's got other things on his mind.
我不想死
I don't want to die!
每个父亲的梦想都是活得比儿子久
It's every father's dream to outlive his son.
虽然我们嘴上都说不愿白发人送黑发人
We all lie and say it's the opposite,
但我现在把真相告诉你了  吉米
but it's time you knew the truth, Jimmy!
-不  -我来了  伯特
- No! - I'm coming, Burt!
不  不
No! No!
伯特
Burt!
这会子吓我可不好
Whoa! Not the best time to startle me.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
和你一样啊  走后门[后庭]
Same as you. Through the back door.
这个梗好
That's a good one.
记下来  护士
Write that down, nurse.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
那是你老公的结肠
That's your husband's colon.
就在那时  老妈看见了
At that moment, my mom saw
老爸身上最恶心人的器官
the most disgusting part of my dad.
但这并没有改变她对老爸的感情
But it didn't change how she felt about him.
尽管她已经快把午饭吐出来了
And even though she almost lost her lunch,
她却更加清楚地明白了她与老爸之间的感情
she gained some perspective on her relationship with my dad.
如果在见识了老爸最恶心的部分之后
If she could still love him after seeing
她依然爱他
how gross he was on the inside,
那老爸也一定会永远爱她
then, of course, he would love her
无论她如何贬低自己的容貌
no matter what she thought about her outsides.
一排撂倒一个就行  西部枪神
Well, that's one in a row for you, Wild Bill.
美国电视剧《死木》台词
我还活着
I'm alive.
是啊  医生说一切正常
Yeah, and they said everything looks great.
其实  看着怪恶心的
Well, actually, it looks disgusting,
但恶心才正常  所以你会没事的
but that's how it's supposed to look, so you're gonna be fine.
你长青春痘了
Wow, that is some zit.
挺可爱的
No, it's cute.
跟你还是个高中生一样
Look like you did back in high school.
但这副眼镜嘛  我就搞不懂了
I don't know about the glasses, though.
每一次我想吻你的时候
Every time I come in to kiss you,
都能从镜片上看到我自己  不得不承认
I see my own reflection, and let's face it,
我已经不是当年的年轻小伙儿了
I'm not as young as I used to be.
我换隐形眼镜
I'll get contacts.
眼镜世界全场五折
They're having a 50% off sale at Glasses Land.
伯特
Hey, Burt.
这个是你的吧
Think this belongs to you.
我的水牛镍币
Hey! My buffalo nickel.
谢谢你  水行侠
Thanks, Aquaman.
他还没从麻醉里缓过来呢
I think he's still feeling the anesthesia.
你干什么呢
Hey, what are you doing?
我们不是说好  不把喜旺的视频
I thought we agreed not to put Hope
传上网的吗
in any videos that we post.
不是的  吉米  我不会上传的
Oh, no, Jimmy, I'm not gonna post this.
我不玩了
I-I'm done with that.
为了这种傻不啦叽的视频争来争去太无聊了
It's dumb to compete over these silly little videos.
你看  我们已经不知不觉地争了好多事了
And, look, we already inadvertently compete over
像是喜旺更喜欢谁啊  谁的发型更好看
Hope's affection and whose hair looks better,
谁是床上小霸主啊
who finishes first in the bedroom.
在下独孤求败
Undefeated.
可不是嘛
Yes, you are.
过来
Hey, you, come here.
吉米上传什么视频了吗
Has Jimmy posted anything?
没有
No.
塞布丽娜呢
What about Sabrina?
啥都没有
No.
那我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
活出自己的人生
I guess we could live our lives.
什么人生
What lives?
快看
Oh, look.
像山羊一样叫的人
"People screaming like goats."
家有喜旺
第四季 第四集
翻译：泽生 小饭 宁馨儿 爵士年代蓬蓬裙
校对：迷藏 宁馨儿    时间轴：加森
后期：随风飞翔      总监：迷藏
■